<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on The Science of Dating</title>
    <link>/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on The Science of Dating</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 07 Sep 2020 21:13:14 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>You can&#39;t put a number to love, but researchers estimated one</title>
      <link>/post/2020-09-07-odds-of-finding-love/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Sep 2020 21:13:14 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2020-09-07-odds-of-finding-love/</guid>
      <description>Dating has drastically changed over the last decades. The modern world now provides new ways to find love, such as online matchmaking and speed dating. Although it’s tough to put a number to love, have you ever wondered what are the odds of finding love?
Working with data scientists from eHarmony, an online dating website, experts from University of Bath calculated that singletons have a 1 in 562 chance of finding love on any given day, considering they leave it entirely to fate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A warm welcome to everyone who&#39;s curious</title>
      <link>/post/2015-07-23-r-rmarkdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Aug 2020 21:13:14 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2015-07-23-r-rmarkdown/</guid>
      <description>Hello there! A warm welcome to everyone who’s passionate about science or simply curious about… dating! I am thrilled to have you around and I’ll do my best on keeping you reading further. Warning! There’s more to come!
If you’re intrigued about who’s behind the scenes, let me introduce myself. I’m Simona Gradinaru, currently a PhD Candidate in Social Sciences at ASE and a full-time Data Scientist at YouGov, living in Bucharest, Romania.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>